<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Concetto</string>

    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="about">CONCETTO is the annual techno-management festival of INDIAN INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY
    (INDIAN SCHOOL OF MINES) DHANBAD. It also refers to the independent body of students who
    organize this event along with many other social initiatives and outreach programs around the
    year. CONCETTO is known for hosting a variety of events that include competitions, exhibitions,
    guest lectures as well as workshops. CONCETTO is Eastern India’s Largest Technical fest
    organized by the student body of the college.

    The word “Concetto” means an opinion, an idea that has the revolutionary potential to shake the
    technical world.

    Started in 2012, with the aim of providing a platform for the Indian student community to
    develop and showcase their technical prowess, it has now grown into East India’s Largest Science
    and Technology Festival with the participation of thousands of students from hundreds of
    Technical Institutes all around the nation. The activities culminate in a grand three-day
    festival event in the IIT (ISM) campus which attracts people from all over the country,
    including students, academia, corporates, and the general public as well. CONCETTO is all set to
    have its 9th Edition from 18th to 20th October’19.

    The 3 day Technical Fiesta of IIT (ISM) DHANBAD- “CONCETTO” is one of the largest
    Techno-Management Fests in Eastern India with a massive participation of more than 10000
    participants from hundreds of different institutes and colleges, who stalk the grounds of IIT
    (ISM) to prove their technical expertise, encompassing a platform to shoot the “TECHNICAL ME” of
    everyone. Apart from the various Robotics and Coding events, Concetto calls all the budding
    Entrepreneurs to showcase their innovative business skills. At the same time, hone your skills
    by joining our workshops taken by the eminent personalities in the various fields of science</string>


    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="Url_coord_asutosh">https://drive.google.com/file/d/1fPIsR1nt5Oiwg89Ad2oGVKEkqcR3rRJx/view?usp=sharing</string>
    <string name="Url_coord_prince">https://drive.google.com/file/d/133osD5fz880hC9tWst0CVC-XlsP6ppUU/view?usp=sharing</string>
    <string name="Url_coord_raghvendra">https://drive.google.com/file/d/135sGVKTVP-FU-09iyLWgwZoPB42_x66c/view?usp=sharing</string>
    <string name="Url_coord_annavarapu">https://drive.google.com/file/d/134yICojfdAXxuJCaQ5R-Rc3cTUw3j0k7/view?usp=sharing</string>

</resources>
